A Florida teenager and an Atlanta woman won the overall men's and women's divisions
Saturday at the annual 7 -mile bridge run.
Vaclav Bursa, 15, of Big Pine Key, Florida, finished first overall.
He completed the race in 41 minutes and 1 second and claimed the top spot in the
men's division. Vaclav Bursa, 15, of Big Pine Key, Florida, finished first overall.
men's division. Bursa won third place in the 2022 race.
is a student at Marathon High School.
Joanna Stevens, 28, of Atlanta, completed the course in 41 minutes and 12 seconds.
Bursa won third place in the 2022 race.
is a student at Marathon High School.
Joanna Stevens, 28, of Atlanta, completed the course in 41 minutes and 12 seconds.
Bursa won third place in the 2022 race.
is a student at Marathon High School.
Joanna Stevens, 28, of Atlanta, completed the course in 41 minutes and 12 seconds.
She won the women's division title and placed second overall.
The race drew competitors from 41 U.S.
states. She won the women's division title and placed second overall.
She won the women's division title and placed second overall.
The race drew competitors from 41 U.S.
There were also runners from other countries, including Canada, the U.K., and
Switzerland.